masterpay.in 2016-04-10

# Masterpay

This Privacy Policy provides you with details about the manner in which your data is collected, stored & used by us. You are advised to read this Privacy Policy carefully before using the services. By visiting Apmultirecharge website you expressly give us consent to use & disclose your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, do not use the services on this Site and terminate the User registration. 

**Note:** Our privacy policy may change at any time without prior notification. To make sure that you are aware of any changes, kindly review the policy periodically

##  General Information

We shall not sell, user personal information to any 3rd party. Any emails and/or SMS sent by Apmultirecharge shall only be in connection with the provision of agreed services & products and this Privacy Policy. 

We reserve the right to communicate your personal information to any third party that makes a legally-compliant request for its disclosure.

##  Consent

By submitting your personal information, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on Apmultirecharge in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including but not limited to your consent for sharing your information as per this privacy policy.

##  Personal Information & Use

The Site uses any information voluntarily given by the User to enhance their experience in the network of the Site so as to make the content useful for the users on the basis of their interest. The Site cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, the Site cannot guarantee that User Content User posts on the Site shall not be viewed by unauthorized persons. Please be aware that every visitor of the Website can access any information that is publicly posted throughout the Site network.

To provide you with some of the features that the site community offers to its Users, Personal Information may be used that is stored in User profile after User has requested such features, for example to send invitation e-mails to people that you specified as being interested in joining the community.

##  Links to Other Sites

Our site links to other websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. Apmultirecharge is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites.

##  Security

Apmultirecharge has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access.
